(The shooting in the studio is continued until the late night!)
(Finally LOOΠΔ's music video shooting is over!)
Kim Lip: Okay, the music video shooting was very long
(All the members of LOOΠΔ, thank you for your effort!)
Kim Lip: I'd like to appreciate everyone here
Kim Lip: Because you guys did a great job even though this shooting was continued very long time!
Kim Lip: We will have a lot of promotional activities~
Kim Lip: Please give us a lot of your love and support!
(Lastly, the trend icon of LOOΠΔ, Yves suggesting the members to do something!)
Yves: Sometimes we have fun doing this gesture when the line 'I love this feeling' come out~
Yves: It's called 'Hi HaHIP'
Yves: How about doing it on the stage?
Yves: In the dreams
All: Love love love love, I love this feeling
(LOOΠΔ's hip hop swag)
(Thank you for watching the LOOΠΔ TV for LOOΠΔ's debut as a full group)